lee yon e
kim yong gwan
and also Park Yoon Woo
descendant of muldu
all names and events are fictitious
any coincidences are random
drug use is a crime
which entails the destruction of personality
and also negatively affects your 7 and the environment
if only money fell from the sky
we have one too
200000000 won 200000000
I'm ready for anything for my family
no, no one will take anything away from us
and you won't die
you and I will do business together
he sells drugs
but he is the most decent in this area
We will earn 100,000,000 in 2 weeks
then we'll talk let's go
Well, how do you like 1 deal?
give me my money back you bastards
I'll earn 200,000,000 and leave
then let's trade
only together
the person died
and you thought
we will just earn money and live happily
don't fool yourself
you are such a criminal
it's James, he's the bad person, not you
I can't do it anymore
and then I thought
what's worse
deal with debts
or with all this
you want money
unless you're going to torture me
then don't tie it up
damn sucker
and then I will destroy everyone
everyone you love
everyone you try so hard to protect
let's get rid of chant haegu
so as not to tease
episode 11
Hansel and Gretel
who is gnawing my sweet home
suddenly the door opens and an old woman comes out
old old woman
she locked Hansel
and then several days and nights passed
yeah, I don’t even know how to get there
how to get inside
stupid said the old woman
but the place near the stove is so wide
that I could get in there myself, yes
banana milk
delicious
why are we moving
because you gave money to your friend
when will mom come back?
ensu
the main thing is not the money
and spiritual wealth
what is spiritual wealth
means to be generous
never steal
and don't offend others
this means that the mistress of the house
my friends and your friends are poor in spirit
I don't like people like that
people who are poor in spirit are bad yes
yes
right therefore
I hope you don't grow up like this
and you won't do that
even with offenders you promise me
then Gretel pushed the witch from behind
that she suddenly found herself in the oven
Yes, and slammed the stove damper behind the witch, you promise
what
doctor doctor
Tangbu District Hospital
thank God you didn't break anything
combat fall skills
how did I end up here
someone called the rescue service
you're lucky without doctors you would have sat back
should I go see a shaman?
This year has been unsuccessful for our team
by the way
why did you go there 1 night
I decided to check the tip from manwon
but I was attacked
from manwon
who are you from
you know it yourself
you should have told us about this in advance
it's dangerous
what about the cameras
yeah the car doesn't drive there
and it was dark and you couldn't see anything
we sent 1 entry for analysis
but
It's unlikely we'll find anything
how long have I been lying here 2 days
what
narcotics department
my phone
disappeared
car
what where is she
wait a minute
yes
who say who you are
Well, that guy who saved
schoolgirl from a bully
what's wrong with him
he's at the station
wants to talk about something
Gwangnam District Police Station
hagu you haven't even been discharged yet
concussion is a serious matter
you can't be so frivolous
why such a rush?
captain chan chief
why did the captain come so early
I don't know, sit down
it's good that you're safe
you're crazy
I can't wait to go to jail
I can arrange
come on
I give up
2 days ago
나
ahh
how are you
and you are you okay
let's run away
we won't be able to live in peace
as long as he is at our side you understand
I have some work to do here
I'm not going to run away my whole life
come to your senses
that revenge is more important than life yes
exactly
Since that day I don't feel alive
what remains for me
You can’t just forget everything and move on
I lost everything
what was dear to me
I
I won't run away
no need
wait, you've been trying to prove it all this time
that he didn't kill anyone
and now he's about to become a killer
we planned the murder together
no
I wanted to save you
he said it himself
the police will be looking for you
if you don't kill him
he will come for our families
this will never end
if he lives
to hell
give up
let's give up
I have nowhere to run
and you won't be left behind
and maybe at least the sentence will be commuted
everyone knows if you tell everything
they'll lose time
tell everything
everything about that night
why did I go there
and who was with me
but for this you have to tell
about our connection
where to start
maybe because of your blackmail
you threaten me
maybe yes
now I understand you
I like it too
your facial expression
I love the expressions on your faces
is it really anticipation?
I feel like I'm close to my goal
I would look at this forever
do they know each other or something?
you are very mistaken
who would believe some criminal
you're right
so as not to be unfounded
today during an undercover transaction
trying to catch you I was attacked
this is self-defense
Why would you listen to me and stay alive?
I'm so tired of it
cooze with you
I think with this
there will be more believers
eh
how will you
take care of your son
will you see him again
who knows
maybe we know it too
some of your secrets
give up
are you serious
then we may definitely not be finished
as you said
taking advantage of other people's weaknesses
you're weakening yourself, it's the same thing
we can make 1 move
the last thing he wants
for us to give up
you yourself understand
who will suffer the most
if everything comes to light
well, ready to negotiate
that I didn't hear
close the case paxua
that's not the point
she said she didn't know yoojeong got her involved in this matter
most likely he will just be put under house arrest
it's a waste of time
then why did you send me to follow her?
you said it yourself
that she might be involved
this is not discussed
free
what
I don't know
the captain has changed so much
suddenly forced to close the Paxua case
fortunately nothing serious
and yet how are you like this
fell
by chance
oh hello
watching you cry ahh
I don't
and by the way
what did you take from the hverim
I took everything for myself
do you mind if you want to make a deal with me
I'll leave them in your car
they would have been immediately confiscated and questions would have arisen for you
you should be grateful
so that's why you saved me
1/2 goods in exchange for life
I think it's a good deal
come on
on this
and we will terminate our cooperation
you almost died recently
take care of your health
make things right with the schoolgirl
I think you can do it
what the fuck
cancer hospital in osyka
what is heavy ion therapy
Zhilio waxes
everything about studying in a high from a visit of entertainment
useful tips for students
air tickets to high
paktojin kanensu paxua
pay confirm purchase
sorry dad
I didn't live up to your expectations
I'm sorry about the new place
everything will be different
I promise
December 8th meeting with investors of Tuin Group
everything is going according to plan
the matchmaker's case will be closed
We'll split the goods and that's it
won't come to us anymore
you should have seen the face of this arrogant bastard
I really wanted to live
that's true, it's a pity
I didn't see this
I will deliver the goods myself
in the meantime, keep it to yourself
when will you return from japan
as I said
200000000 is enough for me
the fact that we didn’t give it back to me
everything else belongs to you
and that's what I understood
tomorrow is the same day
damn
to the director of canfering
wait
to director kankhverim
Incheon City Court
department report victim kim joon ho suspect
nineteen-year-old legion
legion
Leesungsu's father is the chairman of the company, Sungjoon.
take a look at the golden canvas gallery
Golden Hills Gallery
art gallery golden canvas
here are the bastards
express delivery completed
well we'll go bye then
I fell mom will come soon
I wanted to give you a gift last time it didn’t work out
I can buy them for you every day
to fill the room
don't go to America
let's live together
come here
case report
chan haegu urgently
needed money
he urgently cashed out his bitcoins
but this money was not found anywhere
even with relatives
where could it have gone?
such a huge amount
look hard
you are different from chan haegu
the phantom appeared 5 years ago
2 years later they opened a business
let's assume taeguv with govresni
500 per case
for 0 years
where did he keep this money?
money
where did he spend it?
seriously just leave with her
after what she did
if you can't stop
I'll do it don't do it
it'll all be over soon
you suffered because of her
and aren't you even angry?
I can be angry
anyway
we are family
I won't give up 7
and I
are you part of it?
I thought
we have always been family
Do families do this to each other?
Bank of Happiness Manager Ryuhyun Soo
so you stole insu's position
I didn't tell her anything then
because I was afraid that insu
it's going to be hard
having lost his position and his only friend
manager beck
I'll handle family matters myself
so don't interfere
don't even talk
Asua and my wife
I won't accompany you
It's all my fault
why did they throw me out
I didn't know then
it's the end for someone
could be a start
yes I see Choi Kyung Do from his department
captain chan was wounded and hospitalized
can I go and collect things for him of course come in
and what
it's true
well understood
what what happened
anyway
our team will find the criminal
via phone
found in Detective Choi's desk drawer
we have calculated its location
at the time of the crime
based on these data
we brought charges against Choi Gyeongdo
at the request of Detective Choi
we have checked the location of all detectives from the department
and discovered
that 1 other person was in the same place at the same time
and these were
you are captain chan haegu
device location
we're in department 1
we work together
isn't it natural
you intentionally only used your phone near me
plan to blame me
if something doesn't go according to plan
what a disrespect hey gyondo
didn't I save you from paperwork
and took him to his team
and you betrayed me
betrayed
heikindao calm down
I respected you so much
you know
you were my role model
How much longer do I have to listen to this nonsense?
what about the money in your house
800000000
investigation
a search is a search for things that stand out from the general picture
I've been saying this myself forever
that's what I found
decided to update
wallpaper in an old room
This is not declared income, so what?
will you comment?
first time I see
Why would I live in a bug infestation with that kind of money?
it's not mine now
by the way
this is illegal entry
I definitely locked the door
did you break the window
to get through
similar evidence
brushed aside in court
we won't be able to use them in court
but for investigation it’s perfect
and yes that day detective pack
personally asked me to pack your things for the hospital
the landlady voluntarily let me in
I thought you had it all figured out
this world doesn't belong to you
you've grown so much
it would have been like this a long time ago
I had a good teacher
case from haegu
handed over to central administration
curse
you need to copy it
you will do it
yes
I'll ask the fireman just in case
3 years ago
for the first time we stepped on the tail of the Phantoms
after that they found money in my trunk
that's why they were suspended
it was you
that's how damn it is
unpleasant surprise why
I wanted more money myself
why are you complaining
I wonder if they've already left
purchase completed
finally
ligyon
you can't come here
damn
you who what
long time no see
I've been looking for you for so long
and you end up in the house
wow
I'm starting to remember
how you and daddy begged for forgiveness
I remember how you crawled on your knees and swore
that you are ready for anything
Apparently he's ratting behind his back
this is your family
5/10
decided to push me out
putting pressure on shareholders
art gallery
gold canvas lihyok
lip is not stupid
you're in cahoots
you stole my drugs
I don't understand what you're talking about shut up
where is your youngest
this is our last lesson
before the holidays
teacher, how come?
hyuk
I'm sorry
yes
phew what are you talking about
it's worthless
it's nothing
this is from the two of us
thank you
by the way
Sua has no plans to return to Korea again
your case was closed
Yoojeong testified
and did the teacher help?
I'll just say hello and that's it
here
surprise
how old is james
oh or call you ligyon
when they are young they are fed steroids
I didn't even recognize you
are you really wow
by the way
what a beauty
in your room
kanhyurim December 8 meeting with investors of Tuengroup
honestly
I'm even touched
I feel loved
I'll probably reward you for this
I hope you like it
what
you are legion we are from drug control
you are under arrest
for drug trafficking
well, I liked it
damn it's a pity I don't see
I wish I could be there in person
arrest him
you lost again you fool
you have the right to remain silent
whatever you say
can and will be used against you in court
what will happen now
drawing class
teacher
clear everything
almost there
cooperating with the investigation
and pay for your sins
kindo was right
what in this world
everything is not going according to plan
Is this an art teacher or what?
어떻게
oh you
get it
damn it
what what
what
here
I understand you still haven’t recovered from treatment
but time is running out you know
the road won't be long, that's good news
put some money in before going to the airport
this is enough for treatment
study and accommodation
money won't be tracked
don't worry okay
and you
you won't fly
I can't
because of the teacher
wow they say
art teacher was a drug dealer
really
Jinha's mom shopped with him wow the article came out I'm stunned
art teachers
high school student arrested on drug charges
police opened a criminal case against an art teacher
who was allegedly involved in drug trafficking
no if you are noticed with me
you may be banned from leaving the country
you fly first
as soon as everything is resolved
I'll fly to you right away
I won’t fly without you dear
you want me to live
for money exchanged for you
I can't die better
what kind of nonsense are you talking about
Do you even know what lengths I went to for your treatment?
you really are
how can I live
knowing what you had to go through because of me
thought about it
I
I'm terrified you know
it would be better
I'd rather then
fell from the hospital roof
not true
it's not that good, I'm dear
I can't live without you, you understand
1 thought
that you will leave my life
unbearable for me
that's why it's like this
Is it too much to ask?
I've never been greedy
I just want to live with you
sua in our house you understand
ensu
just
drop everything please
don't be stupid
what about your treatment?
what will we live on
we will need money
we can live without them
we always got out
so
leave everything and go
then everything will end
give up everything, forgive your sins
be with us
I'll wait
I will share the pain with you
I will protect you from judgment
it won't be easy for wasp
but the main thing is we will all be together
operating room
doctor
I'm sorry I couldn't save him
how did detective pack die?
why why
try again
I'm sorry please please
you promised to catch the criminal
why don't you keep your promises
let's give up together
how are you
I'm thirsty
water
who are you
dear beloved
I'm not in the mood
just answer my questions okay
kötem dinge
and the product
where
everything is in a personal safe
here is the address and password
hold
siul district gangnam street
I'm not lying
it's really all there
something doesn't add up
misfortune what I hate most is injustice
I'm just shocked
choi messed up himself
and blamed it all on me
Once in the state, everything is possible
only in words
no discrimination
they won't even sit at the table with us
well yes
does he work during lunch?
I'll have to go
what are you going to finish first?
bon appetit
bank of happiness staff recruitment
your name is insu too
kanensu yes
I'm from the HR department
I know the employees by name clearly
and they respond well to you
they say you are diligent
and hardworking
thank you, that's where my talents end
these are truly talents
be diligent
very difficult
not everyone can
아하 감사합니다
let's go here
hello we will join you hello
I'll introduce you
this is the boss dream
we came here in 1 year
this is boss kim
and this is the boss
that genie talked a lot about you
nice to meet you
translated voiced by mobile television studio
commissioned by the online cinema IVI in 2025